{
    "subject": "resource/Archbishopric_of_Bremen",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Basdahl",
    "human_readable": "The capital of Archbishopric of Bremen is Basdahl.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9493495225906372,
            "question": "What is the capital of the Archbishopric of Bremen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7173144817352295,
            "question": "Are there other cities within the Archbishopric of Bremen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7145853638648987,
            "question": "When was Basdahl established as the capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5833041667938232,
            "question": "What kind of entity is the Archbishopric of Bremen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5758980512619019,
            "question": "Is Basdahl a city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5285034775733948,
            "question": "Where is Basdahl located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41223394870758057,
            "question": "What are some important buildings or landmarks in Basdahl?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36474886536598206,
            "question": "What is the population of Basdahl?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3154385983943939,
            "question": "How has Basdahl developed over time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09642796963453293,
            "question": "What does the term 'capital' refer to in this context?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of Archbishopric of Bremen is Basdahl.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9234_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has Basdahl developed over time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9234_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the population of Basdahl?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9234_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some important buildings or landmarks in Basdahl?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9234_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9234_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9234_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9234_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9234_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9234_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9234_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9234_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9234_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9234_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9234_5.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text states that the Archbishopric of Bremen had its seat in Bremen, not Basdahl.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nReasoning:\nThe documents contain information about the Archbishopric of Bremen, but they do not mention Basdahl as its capital. In fact, one of the documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9234/re-ranker-msmarco/11.txt) mentions that St Willehad chose Bremen as the city of his see and built a cathedral there, which is mentioned for the first time in documents of 782. This suggests that Bremen was an important location in the region around the Lower Elbe and the lower Weser, but it does not mention Basdahl as its capital."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not provide any information suggesting that the capital of the Archbishopric of Bremen was Basdahl. Instead, they mention that St. Willehad chose Bremen as his see and built a cathedral there in 789, indicating Bremen itself served as the capital for the Bishopric of Bremen from 804 to 848. There is no information linking this bishopric or archbishopric directly to Basdahl as its capital."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}